

PROFILE-

Data Science and Machine Learning Expert with two years of teaching experience in the relevant field. Areas of interest are Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Artificial Intelligence and Soft Computing.

Energetic software developer with 1+ years experience developing robust code for high-volume businesses. Currently working as a Java Developer at LCEPL PVT. LTD.

PERSONAL-

D.O.B 26 FEB 1990

LANGUAGESENG | HIN | MAR | URDUHOBBIESFOOTBALL | HALAMADRID

CONTACT -



+91 8149448939

+91 8329587191



asrar60@gmail.com asrar2602@outlook.com



Sufiyan Nagar 2, Walgaon Road Amravati MS-India- 444601

SOCIAL MEDIA -



www.linkedin.com/in/asrar-ahmad-4a2b4a64



www.facbook.com/asrar786



twitter.com/Asrar2602

ASRAR AHMAD

Software Developer

EXPERIENCE

May 2017-Jun 2018

Expert WebSoft Pvt. Ltd

Junior Software Developer

- Analyze users' needs
- Designing and coding
- Design each piece of the application and plan how the pieces will work together

2015-2017

SGB Amravati University

Visiting Assistant Professor

- Teaching theory and practical in the Post Graduate Department of Computer Science & Engineering
- It includes Data Mining, Machine Learning and Soft Computing

EDUCATION

2012-2015

M.E in Computer Science & IT

- Major in Data Science and Machine Learning
- CGPA: 8.11

2007-2011

B.E in Computer Science & Engineering

- Major in Machine Learning and Pattern Recognition
- Percent: 67.78 %

2006-2007

Higher Secondary School (HSC)

- Maharashtra State Board
- Percent: 83.83

2005-2006

Secondary School (SSC)

- Maharashtra State Board
- Percent: 79.46 %

SKILLS

JavaScript C/C++ HTML/CSS